What is the biggest misconception that you feel people have about Black resistance?
That it's criminal.
That any time you see someone engaged in defiance, what they are doing is illegal.
And needs to be, like, prosecuted to the full extent of the law.
Or that if it's not criminalized, it's immoral.
Oh, we shouldn't be doing this.
You know, yeah, that's what happens.
Black resistance gets a bad rap.
What's one thing you said in this episode that you stand 10 toes down on?
Coalition building.
I think coalition building is so important.
We cannot do this work alone.
We cannot do this work in isolation.
It is an all-hands-on-death approach.
And that is the only way we're going to get free.